# <u>ISAMU ISOZAKI</u>

#### BACKEND DEVELOPER OR MACHINE LEARNING DEVELOPER

# **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Focused Computer Science major (3.98 GPA) currently attending Drexel University, with 1+ years of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of Database design, Website design, and Machine learning skills to successfully fill the Backend Developer or Machine Learning Developer role at your company. Praised as hard-working by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

Kiara, Shibuya, Tokyo / Jul 2020 - Present

- Setup mail server on Aws so that mail can be received
- Processed and translated mails sent to mail server using milters and Node Js with MongoDB
- Used React Js for the website and firebase for authentication so that users can register

#### **AI INTERN**

Team AI, Shibuya, Tokyo / Jun 2019 - Sep 2019

- Finetuned GPT-2 from Open AI to make Joke Generator for a technical demonstration of the company
- Adapted face2face to make a basic Deepfake for CEO for a potential future zoom avatar

# **PROJECTS**

#### **CHESSKATEERS**

Feb 2020 - Jun 2020

 As part of the CI101 course at Drexel, made an online multiplayer game with React Js Frontend, Node Js backend, and Unity for the game itself

#### **TACTIC GAME**

Nov 2018 - Present

 Made military strategy game with Pymunk and training using OpenAl baseline

- isamu.website@gmail.com
- (267) 285-6836
- 3200 Chestnut St Room 6008, Philadelphia, PA, 19104

#### **EDUCATION**

# **DREXEL UNIVERSITY**

**GPA: 3.98** 

### Philadelphia, PA

Bachelor of Computer Science Computer Science Candidate (Expected graduation Jun 2024)

#### Awards & Honors

- Dean's List
- Dean's Scholarship

#### Extracurricular Activities

- Drexel Al
- ML Reading Group Directed by Dr. Edward Kim

## **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Language: Japanese-Native

Programming: C#, Python, Javascript, CSS, HTML

Tools: Git, Unity, VS Code, Atom, AWS, Ionos, Vim, MongoDb Atlas

Frameworks: Tensorflow, Keras, Pytorch, Numpy, Pandas, React Native, React Js, Mongoose

Operating Systems: Windows, Ubuntu

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Udacity Frontend Development Nanodegree